[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Java was deleloped by ?",
"a": "Elon Musk",
"b": "Sachin Pathak",
"c": "Prince Kumar",
"d": "James Gosling",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "Java is a ?",
"a": "Database",
"b": "Programming Language",
"c": "Operating Syster",
"d": "Brower",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Java code runs on ?",
"a": "Browser",
"b": "CPU directly",
"c": "JVM",
"d": "SQL",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Which one is a loop in java ?",
"a": "repeat",
"b": "jump",
"c": "next",
"d": "while",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Java is ?",
"a": "Complied",
"b": "Interpreted",
"c": "Both",
"d": "None",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "Keyword to create object ?",
"a": "create",
"b": "make",
"c": "class",
"d": "new",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Used to break loop ?",
"a": "exit",
"b": "stop",
"c": "return",
"d": "break",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Which is a valid data type ?",
"a": "number",
"b": "string(lowercase)",
"c": "digit",
"d": "int",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Used to define a constant ?",
"a": "static",
"b": "const",
"c": "fixed",
"d": "final",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "Keyword for inheritance ?",
"a": "class",
"b": "parent",
"c": "inherit",
"d": "extends",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
}
]